Guide to the Mae and Harry Millstone Papers WAG.303
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III. Family, 1910-2008; 2.75 Linear Feet in 2 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, and 1 oversize flat box.; 4 audiocassettes
  This series contains material related to Mae and Harry's shared interests as a couple and a family. A scrapbook in this series contains clippings, photographs, and ephemera related to Mae and Harry's accomplishments, the Union 211 softball team, City League Teams in Williamsport, PA, and various local and national union rallies and parades. The majority of the material dates from the early 1940s through the 1960s. Travel-related diaries, loose notes, and a collection of hotel stationary date from the 1970s to early 1980s with destinations which include Morocco, the Philippines, Italy, England, Quebec, and Greece. In this series is a small collection of correspondence, as well as assembled files containing memorial service information and obituaries for friends and fellow labor movement supporters. Labor movement-themed song recordings and printed lyrics are in this series, and also a play program and sound recording for Needles and Pins.
  - Piano Sheet Music, 1910-1950 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook and Loose Material -- Photograph of Union Softball League team, and Clippings on U.S.O. Softball Tournament, Union Parade Rallies, 1942-1966 (Box 20)
  - Limited Edition Art Books -- Song Of Peace, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Limited Edition Art Books -- Edith Segal and Samuel Kamen -- Prints and Booklets, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence-- General, 1967-1998 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence -- Dorothy and Henry Kraus, 1979-1993 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Obituaries, Memorials, and Related of Friends and Fellow-Activists, 1969-2008 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Obituaries, Memorials, and Related of Friends and Fellow-Activists -- Henry and Lorraine Foner, 1997-2002 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Travel -- Hotel Stationary Collection, circa 1960-1989 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Travel -- Diaries -- Italy and England, 1970, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Travel -- Diaries -- Texas, Quebec, and Greece, 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Travel -- Diaries -- Hong Kong, Thailand, Singapore, Bali, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Travel -- Diaries -- Morocco and Philippines, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Labor Movement Music -- Song Lyrics in English and Filipino, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Labor Movement Music -- Recordings of Songs in English and Filipino, 1981 (Box 17, Audiocassette 303.0008)
  - Mix Tape -- Labor Movement Songs, undated (Box 17, Audiocassette 303.0005)
  - Notebook with Lists and Reviews of Films and Books, 1988-1999 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Clippings Re: Son, David Stone's Work, 1995-2001 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - David Millstone Interview, 1998-08-11 (Box 17, Audiocassette 303.0004)
  - Play -- Pins and Needles -- Program, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Play -- Pins and Needles -- Sound Recording, undated (Box 17, Audiocassette 303.0006)
  - Peace Movement-Themed Music Lyrics, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)